http://filmcellsltd.com/privacypolicy.aspx

HOME    |    CONTACT US    |    ABOUT US    |    MY ACCOUNT    |    CHECKOUT    |    WHOLESALE
Items In Cart: 0Cart Total: $0.00
What is a Film Cell?What is a Lit Film Cell?What is a Morphing Mug?
What is a MightyPrint?What is a PremierCell?What is a StarFire Print?
What is a Clue Mug?
Birds of PreyKNEXAGON™ Wood PrintQuarantine CollectionSportsWedding and EngagementWizarding WorldWonder Woman 1984ALL PERSONALIZEDSALE..............2001: A Space OdysseyA Clockwork Orange AnnabelleAquamanArrowBatmanBeetlejuiceBetty BoopBig Bang Theory, TheBlend Cota ArtChristmasChristmas Story, AClassic HorrorComic-Con 2020DC ComicsDisneyEffwords™ElfElvis PresleyFantastic Beasts and Where to Find ThemFantastic Beasts The Crimes of GrindelwaldFlashFlinstonesFreddy Vs JasonFriday the 13thFriends The TV SeriesFrosty the SnowmanFull Metal JacketGodfather, TheGone With The WindGoonies, TheGreen LanternGremlinsHarry PotterHarry Potter Best SellersHarry Potter MugsHarry Potter PersonalizedHobbit, The HolidaysHorrorIT Chapter 2IT MovieJustice LeagueLooney TunesLord of the RingsMarilyn MonroeMarjolein BastinMiscellaneousMortal KombatMusic LegendsNational LampoonsNew LicensedNew Original DesignsNightmare On Elm StreetPacific RimPolar Express, ThePoliticalRampageReady Player OneRiverdaleScarfaceScooby DooShazamShining, TheSmallfootStanley KubrickStar TrekStar WarsSuicide SquadSupergirlSupernaturalThe ExorcistThe NunThomas KinkadeTom and JerryTrend Setters OriginalsTrue CrimeWacky RacesWestworldWhere The Wild Things AreWilly Wonka and the Chocolate FactoryWizard of Oz, TheWonder Woman.............Acrylic KeychainBookmarks (no film)Bottle OpenersClassic MugsCoaster Sets (Glass)Coaster Sets (Hardboard)Curved Acrylic PrintsFace MasksFilmCell BookMarksFramed Movie ArtFramesHanging AcrylicHanging Glass PrintsHanging Metal PrintsKey ChainLarge FilmCell PresentationsLED Back Lights and FramesLightCellsLuggage TagsMetal PrintsMightyPrint™ Wall ArtMinicellsMorphing Mugs®Morphing Mugs® Clue MugsPhotobookPremierCellSketchbooksStarFire Prints Glass PrintsTrendyPrint Wall Art
.............Login & Registration
Wholesale Info.
Wholesale - Back Lights Film Cell Back Lights
Your satisfaction is always important to us. That includes making sure we protect your privacy and keep you aware of anything concerning personal information.  If you have any questions concerning our privacy policy, at any time, please email us at cs@trendsettersltd.com. We’re happy to help.
This privacy policy has been updated as of May 24, 2018. We added information about unsubscribing from newsletters and how to unsubscribe from your account on Trend Setters Ltd., FilmCells Ltd., or Custom Photo Prints.
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature.
When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes.
Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the “Do we use 'cookies'” section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
How do we use your information? We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
To quickly process your transactions.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.
How do we protect visitor information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.
Do we use "cookies" Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Chrome, Firefox, Internet Explorer, etc.) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term outside parties does not include Custom Photo Prints, FilmCells Ltd., or Trend Setters Ltd. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us? To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the My Account section. Simply uncheck the box that says, “Sign up for our ad, exclusive offers and more.” Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production. To delete all your online account information from our database, sign into the My Account section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction to service that transaction and for record keeping.
We use third party sites for things like newsletters, giveaways, and social media. Our site contains links to other sites, including, among others, those of some of our customers. Those other sites may have privacy policies that may be different from ours. Visitors using such links should consult the privacy notices associated with those links. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online—for example, via message boards or chat rooms—that information can be collected, intercepted and used by people you do not know. Our policies do not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond our control. We take no responsibility for information collected by third parties.
If you prefer to no longer receive our newsletters that are sent through Mailchimp, simply click “unsubscribe” at the bottom of the email.
Third party links In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).
Changes to our policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on May 24, 2018.
Questions and feedback We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue. cs@trendsettersltd.com
Online Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.
Your consent By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
CHILDREN
Our Site is not intended for use by children under the age of eighteen (18). We do not knowingly allow children under the age of eighteen (18) to register for any service, and we do not knowingly collect any Personally Identifiable Information from children under the age of eighteen (18).
Again, if you have any questions about this, email us at cs@trendsettersltd.com. We want to make sure that you have a clear understanding of your privacy rights and how we use your information.
About Us
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Login & Registration
Shipping Information
Visit Our Sister Company, CustomPhotoPrints
What is a Film Cell?
Film Cell Back Lights
What is a PremierCell?
What is a StarFire Print?
Wholesale Info
